Guide to the Robert W. Taylor Papers M2281
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 7. Awards and Recognition
  - National Medal of Science Ceremony Program (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Internet Hall of Fame Certificate (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Student Technology Round Table Pamphlet (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Washington Post Article on National Medal Ceremony (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NSTMF Fact Sheet (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - National Medal Ceremony Photos from White House (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - National Medal of Technology Ceremony Briefings (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - National Medals of Science and Technology Invitation (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - National Medal of Technology Misc. Documents (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - National Medal of Technology Slides (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - National Medal of Technology Award Announcement (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Draper Prize Publications (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Computer History Museum Tribute, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - UT Austin Nomination, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - ACM Awards, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Series 8. Conferences, Lectures, etc.
  - "Bob Taylor Speech Bermuda 10/12/89" Cassette Tape (Box 30, Object 8)
  - "Some Reflections on Early History - J.C.R. Licklider", January 1, 1986 (Box 32, Object 6)
  - "ACM History of Personal Workstations Conference - Conference Exerpts" Videocassette (Box 32, Object 2)
  - "History of Personal Workstations - Alan Kay, 1986" Videocassette (Box 32, Object 1)
  - "Trellis Data Compression" Eva-Tone flexidisc (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "History of Personal Workstations" Labels (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - NAE Annual Report, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - ACM Conference on the History of Personal Workstations (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - CRA Workshop - Quail Lodge, 1994-02-08 - 1994-02-11 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - History of Personal Workstations Conference - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Conferences - 1970s - 1980s (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Series 9. Computer Program Manuals & Instructions
  - Computer Program Map (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Civilization" FAQ (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Programs (Box 9, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Games (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Laurel Manual" File, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Topics in Computer Graphics" - Sproull, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "DEC System10 Mathematical Language Handbook", 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Bravo Course Outline", 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - LISP, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - TENEX Executive Language, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series 10. Related Publications
  - "Communications of the ACM", 2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "The Phi Gamma Delta", Spring 2010 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Geowissen", No. 27 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Publications on JCR Licklider (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Herzfeld - "The Information Age is Upon Us..." (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - SDI, David Parnas (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Science", 1985-04-26 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - News Clipping, 1984-01-16 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "A New Breed: The Software Engineer", 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "Perlis' Programming Epigrams", 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - General Interest Reprints (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lee Sproull - 1980s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Computers and Automation - Reports (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Knuth's 'The Dangers of Computer Science Theory', 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 'Problem Areas in Waveform Processing' (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 'Technology and the Military', 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vannevar Bush (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "What is Computer Science" and Carnegie Mellon Papers (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "The Compatible Time-Sharing System" - M.I.T., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Licklider Papers, etc. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General Interest Reprints - Psychology (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Papers and Reprints in Acoustics (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Decibel", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series 11. Other Work
  - Digital/Compaq Consulting (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - University of Utah (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photos - NASA (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NASA (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ACF Industries (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photo - Martin (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Howey Academy, 1959 - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jobs, 1950 - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series 12. Miscellaneous Media, Slides, etc.
  - "Packaging TNT" Dysan Floppy Disk, 1988-05-16 (Box 33, Object 3)
  - Data DVDs (Box 33, Object 2)
    Approximately 20 data DVDs.
  - Data CDs (Box 33, Object 1)
    Approximately 65 data CDs
  - Circuit Board (Box 38, Object 1)
  - Roll of Negatives (Box 37, Object 1 - 3)
  - Roll of Negatives (Box 36, Object 1)
  - "Apocrypha" 3/4" Film Reel (Master), 1987-12-11 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - "Apocrypha" 3/4" Video Reel (Edited Master), 1987-12-11 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - "The Apocrypha of HPW" Videocassette (Box 32, Object 7)
  - "Hammer Falls" Videocassette, 1993-05-14 (Box 32, Object 5)
  - "The History of the Future" Videocassette (Box 32, Object 4)
  - "Noam Chomsky: US Foreign Policy in a Globalized World" Videocassette (Box 31, Object 7)
  - "Sam Fuller" Videocassette (Box 31, Object 6)
  - "NOVA - The Machine that Changed the World" Videocassette (Box 31, Object 5)
  - Unidentified Equipment Slides (Box 28, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Unidentified Equipment Slides (Box 26, Folder 15 - 16)
  - Miscellaneous Slides (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Photos and Contact Sheets (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Series 13. Born and Acquired Digital
  Scrapbook loaned by family for scanning and returned. Images are available on Searchworks: https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/12198079 https://purl.stanford.edu/qz233gr6650
  2.5 terabytes of digital collection material (hard drive with digitized photos, video and audio) is CLOSED until processed.